【The fate that cannot be liberated】
【无法解脱的命运】
[Episode 11]
[第11集]
Master.
少爷。
Rong Yu, I want to tear you apart.
容羽，我要撕碎你。
He Jiuling,
He Jiuling,
come over.
过来。
Master.
少爷。
leave!
离开！
What happened to you last night?
你昨晚怎么了？
I can accept your usual unruliness.
我可以接受你平时的不守规矩。
but why do you
但你为什么
Were you with him last night?
昨晚和他在一起吗？
If anyone else knows about this,
如果其他人知道这件事，
How can I get married in the future?
以后怎么能结婚呢？
I don't plan to get married.
我不打算结婚。
A-And he doesn't understand anything. Don't imagine things.
A-而且他什么也不明白。 不要想象事情。
why your room
为什么你的房间
A mess?
一团糟？
That's because I couldn't sleep last night.
那是因为我昨晚睡不着。
So I practiced some martial arts.
所以我练习了一些武术。
Back off.
退后。
Stand further away.
站远一点。
Why are your lips swollen?
你的嘴唇为什么肿了？
they are?
他们是？
All right.
好吧。
DD-Don't overthink it.
DD-别想太多。
Look at your guilty expression.
看看你愧疚的表情。
You don't need to explain.
你不需要解释。
I totally get it.
我完全明白。
Rong Yu!
Rong Yu!
——He San! - you-
——何三！ - 你 -
He San, you scared him.
何三，你把他吓着了。
Get out of my sight.
滚出我的视线。
Go back to your own mansion.
滚回你自己的府邸吧。
It was Astrology Day a few days ago and everyone was very busy.
前几天是占星节， 大家都很忙。
After seeing him perform well, we let our guard down.
看到他表现出色后，我们放松了警惕。
Unexpectedly, he took the opportunity to leave Xingxiang Pavilion.
没想到他竟然趁机 离开星象阁。
If it weren't for your message, I'm afraid? ? ?
要不是你的留言，恐怕？？？
Forget it.
别提了。
meet him
遇见他
Just a coincidence.
只是一个巧合。
I don't know if this is a coincidence.
我不知道这是否是巧合。
Every time the young master gets lost,
每次少爷迷路的时候，
It seems to be related to you.
好像和你有关系。
But it doesn't seem to have anything to do with you either.
但这似乎也 与你无关。
Has he ever been lost before?
他以前迷路过吗？
He has gotten lost twice in recent years.
近年来，他已经迷路两次了。
The first time was three years ago.
第一次是三年前。
The young master wants to eat wontons on the street.
小少爷想 在街上吃馄饨。
Zhan Ping bought wontons.
展平买了馄饨，
And the young master disappeared in the blink of an eye.
而少爷转眼间就消失了。
Master,
少爷，
I need a prescription to fill my prescription.
我需要处方才能配药。
I can't give you medicine without a prescription.
没有处方我不能给你药。
How about it
怎么样
Do you invite others over?
你请别人过来吗？
Time is running out.
没时间了。
He Jiuling is sick. She needs medicine.
何九龄生病了。她需要药。
Excellent? ? ? Master! Master!
出色地？？？少爷！少爷！
- Master! - Master.
- 少爷！ - 少爷。
Master, why are you here?
少爷，你怎么来了？
let's go. We go home.
我们走吧。我们回家吧。
medicine!
药！
Master.
少爷。
medicine! medicine!
药！药！
Was it February three years ago?
是三年前的二月吗？
how do you know?
你怎么知道？
The other time was last winter.
另一次是去年冬天。
The young master ran further.
小少爷跑得更远。
He said: "He Jiuling is cold."
他说：“贺九菱冷。”
Miss He?
何小姐？
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
I was just a little distracted.
我只是有点心不在焉。
The young master wants to find you.
少爷想找你。
But he doesn't know where you are.
但他不知道你在哪里。
So he went to the cold
于是他就走向了寒冷
And toward where there is water.
并朝着有水的地方。
When we found him,
当我们找到他时，
His feet were frostbitten.
他的双脚都冻伤了。
Blood spurts from his boots
鲜血从他的靴子里喷涌而出
Ice entered.
冰进入了。
Miss He.
何小姐。
why are you crying?
你哭什么？
I am very happy.
我很高兴。
I'm glad you're okay.
我很高兴你没事。
I'm glad you can talk again.
我很高兴你能再次说话。
I'm glad we can meet again.
我很高兴我们能再次见面。
I was so happy that I wanted to cry.
我高兴得想哭。
Then I wanted to cry too.
然后我也想哭。
No.
不。
No, you can't cry.
不，你不能哭。
I like your smile.
我喜欢你的笑容。
In the days to come, you must always smile.
未来的日子里，你要永远微笑。
I once had a plague.
我曾经得过一场瘟疫。
The doctor said
医生说
I only have one month left to live.
我的生命只剩下一个月了。
But I have to survive.
但我必须生存。
Not just for a month.
不只是一个月。
Not just for one year.
不只是一年。
I have to live my life.
我必须过我的一生。
otherwise,
否则，
no one can change you
没有人可以改变你
That smart and talented Rong Yu,
那个聪明有才华的容宇，
You will never be truly happy in your life.
你一生中永远不会真正快乐。
And that winter,
而那个冬天，
I was trapped by the Canglan River in a snowstorm,
我被一场暴风雪困 在沧澜河边，
I'm cold and sleepy,
我又冷又困，
A pack of hungry wolves stared at me.
一群饿狼盯着我。
They are waiting for me to go to sleep.
他们正在等我睡觉。
But I couldn't let them catch me.
但我不能让他们抓住我。
I just shot a snow wolf and got its skin for you.
我刚刚射杀了一只雪狼 ，并为你拿到了它的皮。
I haven't made you a cloak yet.
我还没给你做斗篷呢。
How can I sleep?
我怎么能睡呢？
But how do you know I'm sick?
但你怎么知道我病了？
How do you know I'm cold?
你怎么知道我冷？
Have you read the stars again?
你又读过星星了吗？
What is Xingdu?
什么是星读？
I just know a lot of things.
我只是知道很多事情。
You are the best
你是最好的
in Jialin.
in Jialin.
future,
将来，
Can you stop worrying about me?
你能不能别再担心我了？
I don't deserve it.
我不值得。
what does that mean?
这意味着什么？
I mean, you should stop running around
我的意思是，你不应该再到处乱跑了
And stop worrying people.
并停止让人们担心。
Eat whatever you want
想吃什么就吃什么
And do what you love.
并做你喜欢做的事。
Don't care about others.
不关心别人。
Just make sure you're happy.
只要确保你快乐就可以了。
I'm very happy now.
我现在很高兴。
Then you and Heshan
那么你和鹤山
You should go home happily.
应该高高兴兴地回家。
Let's go home together.
我们一起回家吧。
You should go to your home.
你应该去你家。
I won't go with you.
我不会和你一起去。
Isn't it? ? ?
不是吗？？？
Won't you come together?
你们不一起来吗？
I dont go.
我不去。
I still have unfinished business.
我还有未完成的事情。
Just go to Rongfu and wait for me?
你就去荣府等我吧？
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
You said you would listen to me
你说过你会听我的话
correct?
正确的？
I promise,
我保证，
I'll go to Rong Mansion to see you.
我去容府看你，
OK?
好的？
He Jiuling,
He Jiuling,
Why are you crying as if we were separated forever?
为什么你哭得 像要永远分离一样？
How did you become so stupid?
你怎么变得这么傻了
After spending a day with Rong Yu?
和容羽待了一天之后？
As a man, can't you be more straightforward?
作为一个男人，你就不能 直白一点吗？
He Jiuling dislikes men
He Jiuling dislikes men
Those who are stubborn and indecisive.
那些固执且优柔寡断的人。
The more trouble you make, the less she likes you.
你越是麻烦， 她就越不喜欢你。
do you understand?
你明白吗？
is that so?
是这样吗？
Okay, you'd better go back quickly.
好了，你们还是赶紧回去吧。
Don't let Mr. Rong
别让荣爷
blame him for running away
责怪他的逃跑
Got on Jiuling again.
又上了九灵。
do not Cry.
别哭了。
Rong Yu!
Rong Yu!
- Rong Yu! - Jiuling!
- Rong Yu! - Jiuling!
Jiuling!
Jiuling!
Rong Yu!
Rong Yu!
Don't listen to He San.
别听何三的。
What he said is wrong.
他的说法不对。
Even if others reject you
就算别人都拒绝你
I won't.
我不会。
No matter what you become,
无论你变成什么，
You will always be my best Rongyu.
你永远是我最好的容宇。
Indeed, every creature has its nemesis.
确实，每种生物都有其克星。
I originally thought that for someone like He Jiuling,
我原本 以为对于何九龄这样的人来说，
No man can conquer her.
没有男人能够征服她。
I didn't expect it to be such a man.
没想到会是这样一个男人。
Chenzhou!
郴州！
Yan Zhao,
Yan Zhao,
You have served me for many years.
你已经在我手下服役多年了。
We have walked through life and death together.
我们一起走过了生与死。
We are like sworn brothers.
我们就像结拜的兄弟。
I did not expect
我没想到
you will draw your sword
你会拔出你的剑
Against my family today.
今天反对我的家人。
The evidence is conclusive that you have committed treason.
证据确凿 ，证明你犯了叛国罪。
For the country and family,
为了国家和家人，
For personal reasons, I cannot let you go.
出于个人考虑，我不能放过你。
I just follow orders.
我只是遵照命令。
His Majesty ordered
陛下下令
when you arrive in the capital
当你到达首都时
You will be arrested.
你会被逮捕的。
I hope you
我希望你
It won't embarrass me.
不会为难我。
So His Majesty summoned us
于是陛下召见了我们
Come back to Beijing and catch us.
回京抓我们。
Chenzhou.
郴州。
enough!
足够的！
If His Majesty wants us to die
如果陛下要我们死的话
We have no choice but to die.
我们别无选择，只能死。
Generally,
一般的，
Considering our friendship,
考虑到我们的友谊，
Please don't embarrass the women in our family.
请不要为难 我们家的女人。
Well, I promise you.
好吧，我向你保证。
We will not tie Ms. Li down.
我们不会束缚李女士。
Your servants will also get a decent burial.
你的仆人也会得到体面的葬礼。
Jiuling!
Jiuling!
show!
晒！
Tan?
谭？
Don't go back to the capital.
别回首都了。
what happened?
发生了什么？
The imperial court has no intention of rewarding your family.
朝廷根本就没打算 赏赐你一家。
General He, Master Chenzhou, and Master Qingxing
General He, Master Chenzhou, and Master Qingxing
All have been arrested.
已全部被捕。
If you go back with Master Qiuting
如果你和秋亭大师回去的话
You will also be arrested.
你也会被逮捕。
What?
什么？
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
What happened to Qingxing?
清星怎么了？
【He is a mansion】
【他是豪宅】
how?
如何？
The mansion is crowded with people
府邸里挤满了人
Waiting for us to walk into a trap.
等待我们走进陷阱。
If we enter the mansion unknowingly,
如果我们在不知不觉中进入了宅邸，
We will be arrested.
我们会被逮捕的。
What happened?
究竟发生了什么？
Why is our family accused of treason?
为什么我们家族被指控叛国？
What should we do now?
我们现在应该做什么？
This is a baseless accusation.
这是毫无根据的指控。
There must be a misunderstanding.
一定有误会。
He San, don’t you know the people from the legal department?
何三，你不认识 法务部的人吗？
Okay, let's go find Minister Zhang.
好的，我们去找张部长吧。
He is a teacher in Chenzhou.
他是郴州的老师。
I think he will help us.
我想他会帮助我们。
Let's go now.
我们现在就出发吧。
time is life. let's go.
时间就是生命。我们走吧。
Yang Ying?
Yang Ying?
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
I'm just worried about Qingxing.
我只是担心庆星而已。
Given his character,
鉴于他的性格，
He will not surrender without a fight.
他不会不战而屈人之兵。
I'm afraid
我耽心
He must be in pain.
他一定很痛苦。
Sister-in-law, I'm sorry.
嫂子，对不起。
Since my father and I refuse to plead guilty
既然我和我父亲不肯认罪
No doctor will come.
不会有医生来。
Whether you admit it or not,
不管你承认与否，
No matter what, we cannot escape death.
无论如何，我们都无法逃脱死亡。
Your brother will let me and the baby in my belly be with him
你哥哥会让我 和我肚子里的孩子在他身边
On the road to Hades.
通往阴间的路上。
Our family of three will not be alone.
我们一家三口不会孤单。
Our He family owes you.
是我们何家欠你的。
You don't owe me anything.
你不欠我任何东西。
Found the love of my life
找到了我一生的挚爱
Dying with him brought me joy.
陪伴他死去给我带来快乐。
This is a decision I made four years ago.
这是我四年前做出的决定。
As long as Qiuting, Jiuling,
As long as Qiuting, Jiuling,
It was enough for Yang Ying to escape this disaster .
而杨影能够躲过这场劫难， 就足够了。
Qiuting.
Qiuting.
Jiuling.
Jiuling.
and? ? ?
和？？？
Since I first saw you,
自从第一次见到你，
It’s been 276 days.
已经276天了。
If you spend that much time with your pet, you must be feeling something, right?
如果你和宠物待了那么久，你一定会有什么感觉，对吗？
i don't expect you
我不期待你
Like me as much as I like you.
喜欢我就像我喜欢你一样。
I just hope
我只是希望
You'll give up a little bit of what you love
你会放弃一点点你的喜爱
For He Jiuling, for me.
为了何九菱为了我。
Yang Ying.
Yang Ying.
Qingxing?
Qingxing?
I know the He family is in trouble.
知道何家有麻烦了。
I shouldn't be swayed by personal reasons at that time.
那时我不应该 因为个人原因而动摇。
My fault.
我的错。
I can't drag her into it.
我不能把她拖进去。
Master, it's already late at night.
少爷，已经是深夜了。
Let's go back to bed.
我们回去睡觉吧。
Master.
少爷。
how far
有多远
Is it "the future"?
是“未来”吗？
Is tomorrow the “future”?
明天是“未来”吗？
At.
于。
uncle.
叔叔。
At,
于，
Why aren't you asleep so late?
这么晚了你怎么还没睡？
I'm waiting for someone.
我在等一个人。
she says
她说
She will come to me.
她会来找我。
At,
于，
go to sleep.
去睡觉。
She won't come.
她不会来。
You've said the same thing before.
你之前也说过同样的话。
But I met her.
但我遇见了她。
But this time, it's true.
但这一次，这是真的。
over there!
在那边！
Catch them!
抓住他们！
stop!
停止！
release!
发布！
go!
去！
Jiuling!
Jiuling!
let's go!
我们走吧！
Jiuling, hold on.
九龄，坚持住。
stop!
停止！
After them!
在他们之后！
Jiuling,
Jiuling,
hang on.
不挂断。
Jiuling.
Jiuling.
Searching over there they can't get very far.
去那边搜一下 他们不可能走得太远。
Go back and look carefully again.
返回并再次仔细查找。
Yes.
是的。
Yang Ying?
Yang Ying?
I'm here. Come pick me up.
我在这儿。来接我吧。
I'm not afraid of you.
我不害怕你。
Don't let her get away.
别让她跑了。
Come if you dare.
如果你敢的话就来吧。
stop!
停止！
Are you guys?
你们是吗
Not full?
未满？
You can't even catch up with women.
你连女人都追不上。
Quickly? ? ?
迅速地？？？
Write a letter to your senior brother? ? ?
给师兄写信？？？
Senior brother? ? ?
师兄？？？
Jiuling!
Jiuling!
do not scare me.
别吓我。
I will definitely find a way.
我一定会想办法的。
I will definitely find a way
我一定会想办法
To save our families.
为了拯救我们的家人。
It's just you and me now.
现在只有我和你了。
Jiuling.
Jiuling.
Your bones are pretty strong.
你的骨子还算硬朗。
Whether you admit it or not,
不管你承认与否，
You have been convicted.
你已经被定罪了。
General He,
何将军，
Even if you don't think about yourself,
即使你不考虑自己，
You should think about your family.
你应该考虑一下你的家人。
Can you bear to see me?
你忍心见我吗
Are you going to torture and interrogate Jiuling like this?
就这样折磨审问九菱？
Speaking of which,
说到这，
my family suffered a lot
我的家人受了很多苦
and suffered a lot of neglect
并遭到许多冷落
these years
这些年来
because of her.
因为她。
My nephew's career was ruined.
我侄子的事业也毁了。
But since then,
但从那时起，
His ability to torture people
他折磨人的能力
Even better than the Department of Justice.
甚至比司法部还要好。
I handed He Jiuling over to him.
我就把贺九菱交给他了。
General He,
何将军，
What do you think about this?
你对此有何看法？
Have you found her?
你找到她了吗？
It's just a matter of time.
这只是时间问题。
Lord Song!
宋主啊！
Mr. Song,
宋大人，
We caught Yang Ying.
我们抓到了杨影。
General He.
何将军。
General He,
何将军，
I have good news for you.
我有好消息告诉你。
He Jiuling had already escaped.
贺九菱已经逃跑了。
But we still got something today.
但今天我们还是得到了一些东西。
Father!
父亲！
——Yang Ying. - I'm not a patient person.
——杨颖。 - 我不是一个有耐心的人。
I don't want to wait too long.
我不想等太久。
I'd love to try some of the punishments I plan to give Jiuling
我很想尝试一些 我打算给九灵的惩罚
in her.
在她的。
to try or not to try
尝试或不尝试
It's up to you, General He.
就看何将军你了。
Do you plead guilty?
你认不认罪？
you hope to!
你希望！
If you want anything, come to me!
有什么想要的就来找我吧！
I, Yang Ying, am not afraid of you.
我杨影不怕你。
you!
你！
Yang Ying?
Yang Ying?
You beast!
你这个禽兽！
- Yang Ying? - You villain!
- 杨影？ - 你这个恶棍！
Yang Ying! Yang Ying!
Yang Ying! Yang Ying!
You beast!
你这个禽兽！
If you have any questions, come to me!
有问题就来找我吧！
two? ? ?
二？？？
I have divorced her.
我已经和她离婚了。
I already? ? ?
我已经？？？
[Divorce Letter] I have divorced her.
[离婚信] 我已经和她离婚了。
She is not from the He family.
她不是何家的人。
she is not.
她不是。
- Yang Ying! - Qingxing???
- Yang Ying! - Qingxing???
Qingxing,
Qingxing,
if you divorce me
如果你和我离婚
You might as well kill me.
你还不如杀了我。
Yang Ying???
Yang Ying???
I plead guilty.
我认罪了。
General He,
何将军，
What did you say?
你说什么？
louder please.
大声点。
I said
我说
I will plead guilty.
我会认罪。
I, He Liang,
I, He Liang,
Used my daughter's name
用了我女儿的名字
Communicate with Xunnan.
与寻南沟通。
I, He Liang,
I, He Liang,
i am a sinner
我是罪人
Who committed treason.
谁犯了叛国罪。
Let my family hurry up.
让我的家人快点吧。
Master Qiuting,
Master Qiuting,
Will you still ask for help?
你还会寻求帮助吗？
Take good care of her.
好好照顾她。
Hello, Your Highness.
您好，殿下。
[Prince Yong’s Mansion] Everyone else is waiting for your orders outside.
【雍亲王府】 其他人都在外面等候您的吩咐。
Let's enter the palace.
我们进入宫殿吧。
Your Highness!
殿下！
I have to go to Jialin.
我得去嘉林。
Your Highness?
您殿下？
We don't have time, Your Highness.
我们没有时间，殿下。
Now that the king is dead,
既然国王死了，
- It's time-- - But in Jialin? ? ?
- 是时候了 -- - 但在嘉林？？？
Your Highness, no matter what
殿下 不管怎样
We should focus on the present moment.
我们应该关注当下。
Jiuling is in danger.
九灵危在旦夕。
Your Highness!
殿下！
You have kept a low profile for 20 years.
你已经低调了20年。
Isn’t it just for this day?
不就是为了这一天吗？
Victory or defeat will be decided at this moment.
胜败将 在这一刻决定。
if you give up now
如果你现在放弃的话
It's not worth it.
这是不值得的。
Your Highness, please think again!
请殿下再考虑一下！
Senior brother,
师兄，
help me.
帮我。
Senior brother.
师兄。
Father. Father.
父亲。父亲。
No, father.
不，父亲。
Jiuling,
Jiuling,
sorry.
对不起。
Head to the palace.
前往宫殿。
My father's subordinate,
我父亲的下属，
Colleagues from Chenzhou,
郴州的同事们，
Dear military comrades in Qingxing,
庆兴的军友们，
And my good friends? ? ?
还有我的好朋友们？？？
I've reached out to everyone.
我已经接触到了所有人。
No one wants to help us.
没有人愿意帮助我们。
Master Qiuting,
Master Qiuting,
At dusk today,
今天黄昏时分，
General He and others will be taken to the cell at Liudaokou.
何将军等人将被押往 六道口的牢房。
They will be executed within three days.
他们将在三天内被处决。
From today,
从今天，
The Department of Justice will search every home looking for suspects.
司法部 将搜查每个家庭，寻找嫌疑人。
[Wanted, Notified] Neighbors or hiders will also be punished.
【通缉、通告】 邻居或藏匿者也会受到惩罚。
Are there any neighbors? Under what law?
还有邻居吗？依据什么法律？
Be careful
当心
To avoid being implicated without knowing it.
以免在不知情的情况下受到牵连。
We have to be very careful.
我们必须非常小心。
now,
如今，
It's better for everyone to be careful.
大家还是小心一点比较好。
[Ministry of Justice]
[司法部]
They are trying to catch General He's daughter.
他们正试图抓住何将军的女儿。
- move! - and their youngest son.
- 移动！ - 还有他们最小的儿子。
Yes.
是的。
They are trying to capture General He's daughter and son.
他们正试图 抓住何将军的女儿和儿子。
What are their names?
他们的名字是什么？
Here they come.
他们来了。
let's see.
让我们来看看。
It seems they have been tortured.
看来他们已经受尽折磨了。
The criminal He Liang,
罪犯何亮，
He Chenzhou,
He Chenzhou,
He Qingxing,
He Qingxing,
Li, Yang
李、杨
Convicted of treason.
被判犯有叛国罪。
The entire family will be executed.
全家人都将被处决。
This is too tragic.
这也太悲剧了。
The execution will take place three days later at Liudaokou.
三天后将在六道口执行死刑。
The criminal He Liang,
罪犯何亮，
He Chenzhou,
He Chenzhou,
He Qingxing,
He Qingxing,
Li, Yang
李、杨
Convicted of treason.
被判犯有叛国罪。
The entire family will be executed.
全家人都将被处决。
The execution will take place three days later at Liudaokou.
三天后将在六道口执行死刑。
The criminal He Liang,
罪犯何亮，
- He Chenzhou, - Get out!
- 何辰洲， - 滚！
He Qingxing--
He Qingxing--
Get lost now!
赶紧迷路吧！
How dare you tell me to get lost!
你居然敢叫我滚！
You will die soon. Let this be a lesson to you.
你很快就会死掉。 让这成为你的一个教训。
Father!
父亲！
- Father!
- 父亲！
Yes, I will die soon.
是的，我很快就会死。
That's why I'm telling you to get lost.
这就是为什么我告诉你滚开。
Stay as far away as possible.
尽可能远离。
leave!
离开！
How defiant you are!
你多么挑衅啊！
move!
移动！
get lost.
迷路。
Get lost quickly.
快点迷路吧。
move!
移动！
As far away from me as possible.
离我尽可能远。
Get lost quickly.
快点迷路吧。
Move quickly.
动作快点。
Get lost now!
赶紧迷路吧！
Jiuling and I are leaving.
我和九龄要走了。
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
She was not covered.
她没有被覆盖。
Her fever had just gone down.
她的烧刚刚退了。
I don't know either.
我也不知道。
But if we stay here, we will implicate you.
但如果我们留在这里，就会连累你。
I'm not afraid.
我不害怕。
I am.
我是。
- But-- - Say no more.
- 但是 -- - 别再说了。
Don’t embarrass Jiuling either.
也别为难九灵。
You have done a lot for us.
你为我们做了很多。
Jiuling.
Jiuling.
He San,
何三,
when i fall asleep,
当我睡着的时候，
I heard people cursing my father.
我听到人们咒骂我的父亲。
They say my father is a criminal
他们说我父亲是个罪犯
traitor.
叛徒。
That was a dream.
那是一个梦。
I have a clear mind. This is not a dream.
我头脑清醒。这不是梦。
nobody
没有人
Are you willing to help our family?
愿意帮助我们家吧？
We have nowhere to go,
我们无处可去，
correct?
正确的？
My fault. I'm so useless
我的错。我太没用了
gentlemen! gentlemen!
先生！先生！
It's here.
它在这里。
There is a suspicious person here.
这里有一个可疑的人。
- This way. - It's here.
- 这边走。 - 它在这里。
hurry up. Quickly.
赶快。迅速地。
This is the place.
就是这个地方。
right here.
就在这里。
hurry.
匆忙。
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
??? 黄昏夕阳下？？？
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
??? 我千里迢迢去远方？？？
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
??? 月下弹琴？？？
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
??? 这些饮料不会让我忘记？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 你悄悄转身 合上了婚书？？？
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
??? 问天上有多少颗星星？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
??? 我轻轻抚着古筝， 等待着你这样的路人???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
??? 原来你就是我的不解之缘？？？